batteries are leaving flextime could AJ
hey Nathan is for you I to two or three
other people might get the suitor one
day okay you shouldn't tell people your
secrets you know well they don't you you
shouldn't tell people what you're doing
oh well we'll just show you what he's
doing he's building the cage so I can't
get out and telling us all right
spaghetti pigs okay
frequency will go back over a couple of
things real fast condenser makes a car
run if you've got a pointed condenser
okay put out the condenser we've been
there
she don't follow you
Nathan has seen the air-conditioner
yeah yeah I can it seen this Hazuki
video alright tell you how many times
he's watched it but yeah no that's fine
okay the the air conditioner under under
the bonnet of the car is not interfering
with the battery the alternator the
computer the diodes in the alternator
it's not affecting the spark timing
anything alright so Wars a shutdown why
does it car shutdown if you drop out the
condenser or got a faulty condenser you
don't put a condenser in with points and
you got massive spark burns the points
jumps right into the spark plug as you
land for the engine because the wrong
frequency so when you break it all down
everything else what you come back - is
that really what does make engines run
or what multitudes of different things
make engines run okay so yeah you might
say take away the petrol the engine they
run
well people have taken away the petrol
and they put other stuff in there like
alcohol okay what are you gonna do with
alcohol we're definitely going to change
the frequency and that frequency gets
changed by a distributor or something
else if you don't met the know what is
methanol do methanol most of it doesn't
burn funny part
he's got higher octane but most of it
you would think with methanol that
because it's Cola because it's a pure
then you should get heaps and heaps more
fuel economy there are they roughly well
apparently a lot of Cola in the chamber
babies cry man what's in the video all
right okay it's saying your methyl right
if you check it comes out your exhaust
probably pretty well so really what's
happening is it's not burning or but so
what actually is happening um well you
need a bit more of a wetting agents but
the other thing is even though it's
higher octane you say even though I was
going to burn even though it's colder
what actually occurs and everything else
is even on burning but do you need it to
been no it's not evaporate in properly
see your petrol evaporates charges your
air okay three parts of it is wetting
agents for the top rings and there we go
some lubrication and keep my cooler so
you lean off you get hotter but they've
taken these whipper snippers and motor
molars and everything else and when you
turn them off they rev up yeah I'll shut
the fuel down they rev up
what part is it sitting down but that's
because they've got to be too hot and
they went out a frequency but they give
me give me about half an hour ringing
about they start over
he can't replace me these car always on
the phone um so they start these whipper
snippers and made him I was no take him
into certain temperature at the
that frigerator you know that put them
into fridges and they've revived but
instead of dying out running on that
climate here and here you go so don't
stop
okay I'm not saying every family you
just can't drop a distributor into a
motor and hope it's going to go you just
can't turn it anywhere and hope it's
going to go you precisely get that you
also can't use certain kinds of fuels at
certain temperatures near when your
girls and hope they're just going to
fall out because you're gonna try and
put methanol into a flame and standard
car on the road and you fuel tank and
then forget your petrol what's in do
they're just going frame F and Holly how
you're going to go
well you engines not going to run very
good is it if it ever starts just on
methanol so you have to then realtor a
whole lot of different things to make it
compensate to run on that stuff okay so
I'm just giving you a couple little
any-any puts to help ease a bit it to
some degree the light in size giving you
all the answers yet I just don't give me
a little bit of a he'll know it's a fear
come on more questions death no it's not
it's just bringing you to awareness
something lonely all right even
mechanics engineer and you're built was
underwear really really some things so
you have to change everything to suit
methanol and everything else Caliban and
clean air everything else but you use
heaps and heaps and heaps and heaps more
I'm telling my girls got a modified race
car super modified thing I mean he
doesn't go through
I suppose you call it Moss McGowan
he goes through gallons per mile he's
just done ran round the track yeah I
made a screaming but the flipping stuff
I burn the out of your eyes
you know that's out the exhaust ice
things burns and it's not
it hasn't burned that stuff up okay
he's using that with more more get up
and go but if he tries to use petrol
hero and get the guy out of the engine
just concept boys okay so they're using
that but they're getting gallons per
mile
okay got miles begun so it could be
going the wrong direction and such if
you could get that performance out of
your methanol it for what it is how
clean it is man you get really fantastic
miles per gallon but they're not okay so
you figure that one out for yourself but
breaking all them the condenser and
everything else is a frequency device
okay why do you set you your plugs at a
certain gap because of frequency ones
you know it gives a right frequency to
close you'll run the LPG what are you
gonna do with the spark plugs if you got
them on me what you do when you got them
on me we for the best of LPG which is
evaporated petrol you want to run petrol
and LPG which is your wettest state and
your dry state they tell you it's not
really you dry it out you do I'm
evaporate your own petrol you get better
but this LPG isn't really evaporated
petrol okay it's it's why
okay so they regulate all that anyway
but you what you do to your um spark
plugs use have the gap okay if you're
running petrol and LPG you understand
that's a and what that does is gives you
your not so fantastic
LPG bit better than if you had the white
gap not so good
petrol so that's a spark gap on the
spark plug itself drive okay I really
adjust his suit but you know those who
closed it down a little bit you give you
both running if you want to driver let's
go LPG well there's a different setting
but probably fifteen tears it would
appear just as a rough what's the normal
petrol thirty-five
you can't metric the I don't know is
that is it or is it just a figure by
geometric or what is it not that guy
okay because I bring it in smaller okay
without confusing the gap what normally
is there for the Fineman paper good by
itself that's what the spark plugs are
meant for yeah okay
we also found just another idea we just
found something else out to you know I'm
not saying it works with every one of
these or doesn't work properly with all
these but we had this fella
you'll know in read Gregor you know the
artist has already three G okay Reggie
had except Falcon penalty through
belliard's for Bloods Reggie had exit no
not even he does this all right keep
that soars and doesn't it doesn't
anyway beside that um he's a painter he
heard an XF Falcon panel van just ought
one on normal petrol before you know XF
America to run it might not know XF okay
um that would be summary in about
watch seventy-nine models all right
doesn't matter around that they're all
around the same so he got normal spark
plugs in that and so on like that normal
he's got now like chronic distributor in
it
and so I'm running on normal petrels and
then they go over to unleaded well if
you go down later some kind of stank
like it straight up but they should just
tell you movie industry
you'll be fine and what they're doing in
this later model cars I'll get back to
that one I haven't gone often the later
model cars like Falcons and Holden's and
everything else like that when they're
running on the unleaded they don't turn
the distributor which gives you a change
of spark they actually pull the cam and
they turn the valve timing back they
called detune and that makes you
run or if you are a new normal timing
for normal fuels with a normal octane
okay then that you were